(sighs)
(phone line ringing)
(Dave(voice on phone):)Hello?
Hi, Dave.
(Amy:)Uh, it's Amy.
(Dave:)Oh. How are you?
I'm fine. How are you?
(Dave:)Terrific. And pleasantly
surprised to hear from you,
(Dave:)given how I acted
on our last date.
(Amy:)Yeah, well,
(Amy:)we both made mistakes, you know.
(Amy:)I took the last breadstick,
you gushed over my ex-boyfriend
(Amy:)like he was Leonard Nimoy
and you were my ex-boyfriend.
(Dave:)So, to what do I owe
the pleasure?
(Amy:)Well, I was wondering
(Amy:)if you'd like to get dinner
again sometime.
(Dave:)Yes, please.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Great.
Let me just check
(Dave:)my schedule, he said,
(Dave:)trying to seem like a man
with things on his schedule.
(Amy:)How 'bout Saturday?
(Dave:)Uh, hmm...
(Dave:)Let me see. Uh, Friday,
(Dave:)farmers' market with Jay Z.
(Dave:)Sunday, piano shopping
with Elton John.
(Dave:)Saturday works.
(Raj:)Oh. Did you know,
at the United Nations,
(Raj:)there's a Department
for Outer Space Affairs?